<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="change_language_tip">Modifying the game language requires restarting the application.</string>
    <string name="download">Download</string>
    <string name="google_pay_error">Something went wrong. Please check network connection or google service account.</string>
    <string name="like_link_not_set">Like Link not set</string>
    <string name="noadload">No ad fill,please try again later</string>
    <string name="opening_hours">Opening hours :Our team is available Monday - Friday 09:00-18:00 (UTC+8)</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_text">Privacy Policy\nrespects and protects the personal privacy of all service users. In order to provide you with more accurate and more personalized service, the Company will use and disclose your personal information in accordance with the provisions of this Privacy Policy. However,the Company will treat such information in a high degree of diligence and discretion.Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, without your prior consent, the Company will not disclose such information to any third party. The Company will continue to update this privacy policy. At the time you agree to t Service Agreement of the Company, you are deemed to have agreed to all of the contents of this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy belongs to an integral part of the Service Agreement.\n1. Information Use\nThe Company fully respects and protects all personal information submitted and generated by users during use of website services provided by the company. Except as otherwise provided in the terms, the Company, without the prior consent of the user, will not disclose the privacy information of user to any third party. Except with your permission, the third party or the Company individually or collectively serving you will be denied access to your information, including all previously accessible information upon termination of the service.\n2. Information Storage and Exchange\nYour information and data collected by the Company will be stored on the servers of Company and (or) servers of its affiliates. Such information and data may be transferred to foreign countries outside the country or region in which you are currently located, or the location where information and data is collected, and accessed and stored in foreign countries.\n3. Information Administration\nWithout disclosing privacy information of users, the company is entitled the technical analysis of the entire user database, and use it for commercial purposes after such analysis (including, but not limited to publishing, analyzing, or by other means, utilize the access volume of users, access time, preference and other user data).\n4. Using Cookies to Collect Data\nWe may use cookies to collect user data, which helps users when revisiting the site. Cookies are small pieces of data sent by a web server and stored in a web browser so that the data can be read from the browser in the future. Currently, the data collected from cookies is used to improve service function. Data provided by the Company is analyzed and organized based on cumulative use of the service by users. Cookies helps the login process operate faster and more smoothly, and can store data between calls.\nYou may disable cookies in your browser without affecting your experience on our website, but cookies do make our services more convenient. Disabling cookies may make using our service more complicated and involve more input procedures. You should also note that if you disable cookies, some features of the Company services may be affected.\n5. Privacy Policy Update\nThe Company reserves the right to revise the terms of the Privacy Policy at any time. Without prior notice to individual users, we may publish revisions on the corresponding web pages when revising the terms. If a user doe snot agree to the revised content, the user may stop using all services provided by the Company. If the user continues to use any service provided by the company, the user is deemed to have accepted the revised content provided by the Company.</string>
    <string name="product_nohave">The item does not exist</string>
    <string name="ps_all_audio">All audio</string>
    <string name="ps_audio">Access to system recording permission denied</string>
    <string name="ps_audio_empty">You can use system recordings to record audio</string>
    <string name="ps_audio_error">The audio is corrupted</string>
    <string name="ps_camera">Get system camera permission denied</string>
    <string name="ps_camera_roll">CameraRoll</string>
    <string name="ps_camera_roll_num">%1$s (%2$d)</string>
    <string name="ps_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="ps_choose_limit_seconds">Only videos from %1$ds to %2$ds can be selected</string>
    <string name="ps_choose_max_seconds">You can only select videos within %1$ds</string>
    <string name="ps_choose_min_seconds">You cannot select a video less than %1$ds</string>
    <string name="ps_completed">Completed</string>
    <string name="ps_confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="ps_current_month">This month</string>
    <string name="ps_current_week">This week</string>
    <string name="ps_data_exception">Get album data exception…</string>
    <string name="ps_data_null">There no data here…</string>
    <string name="ps_default_original_image">Original</string>
    <string name="ps_done">Complete</string>
    <string name="ps_done_front_num">%1$d/%2$d Ok</string>
    <string name="ps_editor">Editor</string>
    <string name="ps_empty">you can use your camera to take photos or videos</string>
    <string name="ps_empty_audio_title">No audio file\n</string>
    <string name="ps_empty_title">No video or photos\n</string>
    <string name="ps_error">The picture is corrupted</string>
    <string name="ps_gif_tag">gif</string>
    <string name="ps_go_setting">Go Setting</string>
    <string name="ps_jurisdiction">Read memory card access denied</string>
    <string name="ps_know">OK</string>
    <string name="ps_long_chart">Long</string>
    <string name="ps_message_audio_max_num">Select up to %1$s Audio</string>
    <string name="ps_message_max_num">Select up to %1$s images</string>
    <string name="ps_message_video_max_num">Select up to %1$s Video</string>
    <string name="ps_min_audio_num">The minimum audio selection cannot be less than %1$s</string>
    <string name="ps_min_img_num">The minimum selection of pictures shall not be less than %1$s</string>
    <string name="ps_min_video_num">Video Selection Cannot%1$sNumber</string>
    <string name="ps_not_crop_data">No cropped data</string>
    <string name="ps_original_image">Original (%1$s)</string>
    <string name="ps_pause_audio">Pause</string>
    <string name="ps_photograph">Take Picture</string>
    <string name="ps_play_audio">Play</string>
    <string name="ps_please">Please later…</string>
    <string name="ps_please_select">Please Select</string>
    <string name="ps_preview">Preview</string>
    <string name="ps_preview_image_num">%1$d/%2$d</string>
    <string name="ps_preview_num">Preview(%1$d)</string>
    <string name="ps_prompt">Prompt</string>
    <string name="ps_prompt_audio_content">Save audio to phone？</string>
    <string name="ps_prompt_image_content">Do you want to save pictures to your phone?</string>
    <string name="ps_prompt_video_content">Do you want to save video to your phone?</string>
    <string name="ps_quit_audio">Quit</string>
    <string name="ps_record_video">Record Video</string>
    <string name="ps_rule">not pictures or video</string>
    <string name="ps_save_audio_error">Audio save failed</string>
    <string name="ps_save_image_error">Picture save failed</string>
    <string name="ps_save_success">save successfully until</string>
    <string name="ps_save_video_error">Video save failed</string>
    <string name="ps_select">Choose</string>
    <string name="ps_select_audio_max_second">Select audio for more than %1$d s</string>
    <string name="ps_select_audio_min_second">Select audio for less than %1$d s</string>
    <string name="ps_select_max_size">The selected file is larger than %1$s</string>
    <string name="ps_select_min_size">The selected file is less than %1$s</string>
    <string name="ps_select_no_support">Unsupported selection type</string>
    <string name="ps_select_video_max_second">Select video for more than %1$d s</string>
    <string name="ps_select_video_min_second">Select video for less than %1$d s</string>
    <string name="ps_send">Complete</string>
    <string name="ps_send_num">Complete(%1$d/%2$d)</string>
    <string name="ps_stop_audio">Stop</string>
    <string name="ps_take_picture">Shot</string>
    <string name="ps_tape">Tape</string>
    <string name="ps_use_camera">Using camera</string>
    <string name="ps_use_sound">Using recording function</string>
    <string name="ps_video_error">The video is corrupted</string>
    <string name="ps_video_toast">Video not Preview</string>
    <string name="ps_warning">No Media files!</string>
    <string name="ps_webp_tag">webp</string>
    <string name="recharge_cancel">Top-up canceled</string>
    <string name="recharge_failed">Top-up failed</string>
    <string name="recharge_success">Top-up successfully</string>
    <string name="service_policy_text">Terms of Service\nThis Agreement is a contract entered into by the platform member(hereinafter referred to as \"Party A\") and (hereinafter referred to as \"Party B\") on the gaming services provided by Party B. Once registered as a member Party B, Party A agrees and is willing to abide by all of the following terms.\nArticle I Scope of the Agreement\nParty B provides Party A with mobile gaming services and other related services (hereinafter referred to as the Service), Party A shall fully abide by this Agreement and rules of game supervision. With regard to the rights and obligations of the service, both parties shall adhere to terms of this Agreement.\nArticle II Contents of Service\nContents provided by Party B and based on actual circumstances is to offer users rich online resources via the Internet in its own operating system, including a variety of information tools, game links, e-mail, etc.Unless otherwise explicitly stated, any new feature that improves or enhances the current service, including new products, will be unconditionally applicable under this Service Agreement. Party B has the right to expand its services, and services provided by Party B may change from time to time. As for fee-based services, advance notice will be given before the service is made available online.Timing of such advance notice will be at the discretion of Party B. Free service will not require notice, unless Party B considers it to be necessary.\nArticle III User Account (user account, password and security)\n1. User account registration\nUsers must agree to all terms of this Agreement and complete the registration procedure. After a user has successfully registered, Party B will give the user an account and corresponding password. Users will keep their own ID and passwords, and should be responsible for activities under their accounts.\n2. Safeguarding of user account\nIn order to provide this service to Party A, Party B will not disclose name of Party A, address, contact address, e-mail, account number,password or other personal information, unless:\n2.1 Party A authorizes Party B to disclose such personal information.\n2.2 Relevant laws or administrative regulations require Party B to disclose personal information of Party A.\n2.3 Party B needs to disclose such personal information in order to protect its intellectual property and other property rights.\nParty B will take commercially reasonable means to protect personal information of Party A. Party A shall not transfer or lend its account and password to others. Party B does not assume any liability for any illegal use of account of Party A or password by others and resulting consequences due to negligence of Party A in safeguarding its account or password.\nArticle IV Obligations of Party A\n1. Party A provides service-related equipment (such as computers,and other Internet-related equipment) and bears costs (such as telephone charges and Internet access fees).\n2. Party A shall not use the service or participate in activities of Party B via improper or unfair means.\n3. Party A shall not interfere with normal services provided by Party B, including but not limited to:\n3.1 cracking, modifying the client program provided by Party B;\n3.2 making, using, publishing, or distributing any form of tool or program (plug) that may compromise the fairness of the game;\n3.3 exploiting loopholes and procedural errors (bugs) to disrupt the normal progress of the game or spreading the loophole or error (Bug);\n3.4 illegally collecting personal data of others.\n4. Party A must protect its own account number and password, and bear the consequences of the disclosure of its account and password due to its own negligence.\nArticle V Privacy Protection\n1. Party B guarantees not to disclose user registration data or user private contents generated during use of network service to the public do main or any third party.\n2. Party B may cooperate with a third party to provide relevant network services to users. In this case, if the third party agrees to assume the responsibility of protecting user privacy equal to that of Party B, Party B may provide user data to the third party.\nArticle VI Game Supervision\nIn order to supervise the way the game is operated, Party B shall set a fair and equitable rules for the game. Party A shall abide by the rules set by Party B.\nA game supervision rule becomes invalid if it contains one of the following circumstances:\n1. Contradicts any provision in this Agreement.\n2. Deprives Party A of contractual rights.\nArticle VII Limited Warranty and Liability\nParty B only accepts the following limited warranty:\n1. Services provided by Party B are consistent with the service commitments Party B officially announced;\n2. Party B only resolves any issue in the process of providing the service in a commercially reasonable way. In addition, within the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, Party B does not guarantee that the service provided meets all the requirements of Party A. Party B does not assume any liability or damage (including, but not limited to, personal injury, privacy leaks, any liability associated with failing to fulfill good faith or reasonable care, or damage as a result of financial or other loss caused by negligence or any other reason) as a result of use of Party A of the service.\nArticle VIII User Information Storage and Restrictions\nParty B has the right to determine if the user behavior is consistent with terms of service provisions. If Party B deems that the user has violated the terms of service provisions, it has the right to delete information sent by the user or even terminate network services for the user.\nArticle IX Service Change,Suspension or Termination\n1. Party B will give advance notice if network services need to be suspended due to system maintenance or upgrades.\n2. Party B reserves the right to unilaterally suspend or terminate some or all of the network services by issuing prior announcement or giving notice to Party A, and will not take any liability for Party A or any third party for any loss resulting from suspending or terminating services.\nArticle X Fee Policy\nParty B has the right to determine and modify the fee standards and methods. Where fee standards need to be adjusted, Party B will issue notice on the relevant web pages before the adjustment takes effect.\nIn regards to fee charging services, Party A shall purchase the service in accordance with the confirmed fee policy. If Party A fails to do so,Party B may immediately suspend the service.\nArticle XI Disclaimer\n1. Party B does not guarantee any of the following:\n1.1 The service will be provided in uninterrupted, timely, secure,or error-free manner.\n1.2 If a third party has illegally infringed upon the rights of Party A, and Party B has been informed of such infringement, Party B shall assist Party A to remove or identify the infringement.\n2. Party A expressly agrees that it will solely assume all risks associated with use of the network services.\nArticle XII Damage\nIf Party A has breached this Agreement or relevant laws, resulting in damage or derivative expenses taken by parent company of Party B, subsidiaries, affiliates, related companies, employees, agents or other related support staff (including, but not limited to, legal expenses in claims,litigation, or related reconciliation paid to all such persons due to breach of Party A of this Agreement), Party A shall be held liable for such damages.\nArticle XIII Termination of the Agreement\nParty A shall abide by the Agreement and relevant laws and regulations. If Party B has detected any breach of this Agreement or relevant laws or regulations by Party A, Party B is entitled to, without prior notice to Party A, immediately suspending, terminating or deleting account of Party A and all relevant data, files and records, and disqualifying, suspending or restricting membership of Party A.\nArticle XIV Modification and Interpretation\nBy being aware of the ongoing changes of Party B itself, users and the market conditions, if Party A continues to use the service provided by Party B, Party A will be deemed to have agreed to and accepted modifications,addition, and deletion of terms of this Agreement, and therefore is not entitled to any claims or damages.\nTo the maximum extent applicable, the Company reserves the right of final interpretation of this Agreement.</string>
    <string name="sharing_link_notset">Sharing Link not set</string>
    <string name="shouquan_zx_xz_nosdcard">No SD Card</string>
    <string name="shouquan_zx_xz_permission_turn_cammera">Permission to turn on the camera</string>
    <string name="shouquan_zx_xz_readsdcard">Permission to read SD Card data</string>
    <string name="shouquan_zx_xz_refuse">You have refuse the permission once</string>
    <string name="ticket_number">Ticket Number:</string>
    <string name="ticket_number_copied">Ticket Number copied</string>
    <string name="tw_account">Account</string>
    <string name="tw_account_facebook_login">facebook</string>
    <string name="tw_account_input_hint">Enter account</string>
    <string name="tw_account_length_tip">Please enter account of 2 to 30 digits</string>
    <string name="tw_account_login">Log in by account</string>
    <string name="tw_account_login_title">Log in</string>
    <string name="tw_account_notbind">The account has not bound with phone number</string>
    <string name="tw_account_register_hint_account">Letter, number and underline only</string>
    <string name="tw_account_register_hint_password">6 to 20 characters only</string>
    <string name="tw_account_tip">Account</string>
    <string name="tw_account_upgrade">Account upgrade</string>
    <string name="tw_acount_check">Account should be made up by numbers, letters and underline(4-20 digits)</string>
    <string name="tw_addr_kong">The address is empty</string>
    <string name="tw_aggre_auth">Please agree Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="tw_agreement_1">I have read and accepted</string>
    <string name="tw_agreement_2">Terms of Service</string>
    <string name="tw_agreement_3">and</string>
    <string name="tw_agreement_4">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="tw_agreement_check_tip">Please agree the relevant terms</string>
    <string name="tw_agreement_tips">Please confirm the terms to start playing</string>
    <string name="tw_area_tel">{SouthKorea82:82,Janpa81:81,Vietnam84:84,Malaysia60:60,UnitedKingdom44:44,Thailand66:66,German49:49,UnitedStates1:1,Singapore65:65,China86:86,Macao853:853,Australia61:61,Canada1:1,Philippines63:63,HongKong852:852,Cambodia855:855,India91:91,Indonesia62:62,Taiwan886:886,NewZealand64:64}</string>
    <string name="tw_auto_login_tip1">Logging in automatically...</string>
    <string name="tw_bindingemailsuccess">Bound</string>
    <string name="tw_call_center">Customer Service Center</string>
    <string name="tw_change_email">Change email</string>
    <string name="tw_change_mobile">Change mobile phone</string>
    <string name="tw_change_password">Modify Password</string>
    <string name="tw_change_pwd_tip1">Master,bound mail change email has been sent to your binding email</string>
    <string name="tw_change_pwd_tip1_1">Master,bound mobile phone change massage has been sent to your binding mobile phone</string>
    <string name="tw_change_pwd_tip2">Mail verification code</string>
    <string name="tw_change_pwd_tip3">Massage verification code</string>
    <string name="tw_change_pwd_tip4">Valid in minutes, please enter verification code in time</string>
    <string name="tw_changepwd_title">Modify Password</string>
    <string name="tw_check_code">Verification code</string>
    <string name="tw_check_code_">Verification Code:</string>
    <string name="tw_check_code_nil">Verification code can not be empty</string>
    <string name="tw_check_success">Verify successfully</string>
    <string name="tw_checkcode_dif">Entered phone number is not matched with binding phone number</string>
    <string name="tw_checkcode_error">Enter wrong mobile phone verification code</string>
    <string name="tw_checkcode_nil">Please enter verification code</string>
    <string name="tw_choose_email_safe">Master, please confirm your email to improve your account security. When you forget your password, you can reset password by the email.</string>
    <string name="tw_choose_recharge_gw">Other Payments (%1$2d%% Bonus)</string>
    <string name="tw_choose_recharge_tile">Please select top-up method</string>
    <string name="tw_choosepwd_type">Please select retrieve method!</string>
    <string name="tw_choosewentitype">Please select question type</string>
    <string name="tw_confirm_email">Confirm by mail</string>
    <string name="tw_confirm_tel">Confirm by Mobile phone</string>
    <string name="tw_contentnokong">Reply can not be empty</string>
    <string name="tw_copy">Copy</string>
    <string name="tw_copy_success">Copied</string>
    <string name="tw_countdown_service_pre_start">About to Begin</string>
    <string name="tw_countdown_service_start">Start</string>
    <string name="tw_countdown_service_tip">Server Launch Countdown</string>
    <string name="tw_delete_account">Delete Account</string>
    <string name="tw_delete_account_success">Your account deletion request has been submitted, your account is now in the grace period</string>
    <string name="tw_delete_account_tips">Dear player, we regret to inform you that we have received your request for account deletion.\nBelow are important notes regarding the account deletion process. Please read them carefully:\nYou have a 7-day grace period. If you log in to your account again within 7 days of submitting the deletion request, the request will be considered withdrawn. This is to prevent unauthorized use of your account. Logging into the game again within 7 days will cancel the deletion request.\nAfter 7 days, if there are no objections, your current game account will be automatically deleted, and you will not be able to log in to the game using that account.\nOnce the account is deleted, you will not be able to log in to the game again. Items and characters in your game account will be permanently erased. Please proceed with caution.</string>
    <string name="tw_delete_btn_back">Back</string>
    <string name="tw_delete_btn_confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="tw_delete_btn_rollback">Cancel</string>
    <string name="tw_delete_call_service">Your account has been deleted. If you have any questions, please contact customer service.</string>
    <string name="tw_delete_rollback_tips">Dear player, Your account is currently in the deletion grace period, Your account will be completely deleted on %s. If you wish to cancel the account deletion process, please click the \'Cancel\' button.</string>
    <string name="tw_delete_title">Cancellation Terms</string>
    <string name="tw_dis_dis">Describe:</string>
    <string name="tw_disbug">Please describe your problem</string>
    <string name="tw_donot_order">Ordering, do not do repetitive operation!</string>
    <string name="tw_error_input">Please enter the Role Name or Password!</string>
    <string name="tw_facebook_connect_error">Link facebook failed</string>
    <string name="tw_facebook_no_xg_name">If log in through facebook，you can not modify the password</string>
    <string name="tw_find_account">Please enter the account you want to retrieve</string>
    <string name="tw_find_accountv">Retrieve visitor account</string>
    <string name="tw_find_password_server">Retrieve password</string>
    <string name="tw_find_pwd">Retrieve password</string>
    <string name="tw_find_visitor_account">Retrieve visitor account</string>
    <string name="tw_find_visitor_tip1">Please enter the UID and Recovery Code you saved when you first log in 【</string>
    <string name="tw_find_visitor_tip2">】if you lose it, you can not retrieve your account</string>
    <string name="tw_forget_password">Forget password</string>
    <string name="tw_game_tip">Game:</string>
    <string name="tw_geren_zhongxin">Personal Center</string>
    <string name="tw_get">Claim</string>
    <string name="tw_get_checkcode">Obtain verification code successfully</string>
    <string name="tw_get_code">Send verification code</string>
    <string name="tw_get_mail_code">Obtain mail verification code successfully</string>
    <string name="tw_get_order">Obtaining order, please wait...</string>
    <string name="tw_get_orderfail">Obtain order number failed</string>
    <string name="tw_get_record">Claim Record</string>
    <string name="tw_get_record_dis">Pack Content</string>
    <string name="tw_gift_code">Pack code</string>
    <string name="tw_gift_code_num">CDK</string>
    <string name="tw_gift_show_tip">Claim the gift after entering the game</string>
    <string name="tw_google_fail_tip">Google Play initialization failed,payment is currently unavaliable.Please make sure your region supports Google Payment or try again later!</string>
    <string name="tw_google_no_server">Please check if the Google Service is installed</string>
    <string name="tw_google_play_str">Google Play</string>
    <string name="tw_haoping_libao">Praise Pack</string>
    <string name="tw_haveget">Claimed</string>
    <string name="tw_huifu_code_tip">Recovery Code</string>
    <string name="tw_huifuliebiao">Reply List</string>
    <string name="tw_huodong_end">Event ends</string>
    <string name="tw_huodong_nostart">Even is not available now, coming soon!</string>
    <string name="tw_huodong_shuoming">Event Details</string>
    <string name="tw_i_know">I got it</string>
    <string name="tw_img_desc">image desc</string>
    <string name="tw_init_tip">Initializing...please wait</string>
    <string name="tw_input_account">Please enter your new account</string>
    <string name="tw_input_account2">Please enter account</string>
    <string name="tw_input_form_error">Invalid user name of password format</string>
    <string name="tw_input_mail">Please enter your mail</string>
    <string name="tw_input_newpassword">Please enter new password</string>
    <string name="tw_input_old_password">Please enter your old password</string>
    <string name="tw_input_oldpassword">Please enter old password</string>
    <string name="tw_input_password">Please enter your new password</string>
    <string name="tw_input_restpwd">Master, you can reset password by following</string>
    <string name="tw_input_secondpassword">Please enter password again</string>
    <string name="tw_input_telinfo">Please enter massage verification code</string>
    <string name="tw_input_username">Please enter the account which you want to retrieve password</string>
    <string name="tw_int_telcode">Please enter phone number</string>
    <string name="tw_is_logining">Logging in………</string>
    <string name="tw_kefu_choose">You have selected</string>
    <string name="tw_kefu_choose_tip">Please select contact method</string>
    <string name="tw_kefu_copy">Copy</string>
    <string name="tw_kefu_email">CS Mail Adr</string>
    <string name="tw_kefu_evaluate">How would you rate our service?</string>
    <string name="tw_kefu_input_content">Please enter the content</string>
    <string name="tw_kefu_input_title">Please enter the title</string>
    <string name="tw_kefu_no">No</string>
    <string name="tw_kefu_noyes">Has your problem been solved?</string>
    <string name="tw_kefu_online">Online Service</string>
    <string name="tw_kefu_photo">*picture</string>
    <string name="tw_kefu_reply">Replied</string>
    <string name="tw_kefu_select_question">Please select the type</string>
    <string name="tw_kefu_solve">Solved</string>
    <string name="tw_kefu_subsuccess">Submitted</string>
    <string name="tw_kefu_tijiao1">Dear, you have not submitted the problem,</string>
    <string name="tw_kefu_tijiao2">tap the upper right corner to submit your problem</string>
    <string name="tw_kefu_tile">Title</string>
    <string name="tw_kefu_tip">CS</string>
    <string name="tw_kefu_type">Type</string>
    <string name="tw_kefu_wait">Waiting...</string>
    <string name="tw_kefu_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="tw_lift_center">Pack Center</string>
    <string name="tw_liji_haoping">Praise now</string>
    <string name="tw_liji_share">Share Now</string>
    <string name="tw_limit_input_num">0123456789</string>
    <string name="tw_limit_input_password_str">0123456789abcdefghijklmnopqrstuvwxyzABCDEFGHIJKLIMNOPQRSTUVWXYZ</string>
    <string name="tw_lishijili">History</string>
    <string name="tw_loading">Loading...</string>
    <string name="tw_loadup_pic">Upload pic</string>
    <string name="tw_login_ing">Dear surge, logging in game</string>
    <string name="tw_login_sel_fb">Login With Facebook</string>
    <string name="tw_login_sel_google">Login With Google</string>
    <string name="tw_login_sel_guest">Guest</string>
    <string name="tw_login_sel_other_text">Others</string>
    <string name="tw_loginfail">Log in failed</string>
    <string name="tw_logining_tip">Logging in...</string>
    <string name="tw_mail_add_nil">Please enter mail address</string>
    <string name="tw_member_login">Log in</string>
    <string name="tw_member_reg">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="tw_mobile_num">Mobile phone number</string>
    <string name="tw_mobile_zixun">Master, Hello, please fill in mobile phone info and it will become the evidence for retrieving account through customer service!</string>
    <string name="tw_move_hide">Drag here to hide</string>
    <string name="tw_my_toushu">I need help</string>
    <string name="tw_net_error">Network anomaly, please try again later!</string>
    <string name="tw_net_timeout">Network time out</string>
    <string name="tw_network_error">Network malfunction,please check it.</string>
    <string name="tw_new_pwd_length_tip">Please enter password of 6 to 20 digits</string>
    <string name="tw_new_pwd_nul">New password can not be empty</string>
    <string name="tw_no_bind_mobile_email">Not bound with mobile phone or email</string>
    <string name="tw_nohave_account">Not obtaining default account</string>
    <string name="tw_noserver">No server yet</string>
    <string name="tw_password_input_hint">Enter password</string>
    <string name="tw_password_null">Password should be at least 6 characters and case sensitive</string>
    <string name="tw_password_tip">Password</string>
    <string name="tw_pay_record">Top-up history</string>
    <string name="tw_pay_second">Top-up successfully</string>
    <string name="tw_permission_content1">As Android 6.0+ runs this game app, it needs to access the permission. If you deny this permission, the game will be quited.</string>
    <string name="tw_permission_content2">As Android 6.0+ runs this game app, it needs to access the permission. Please allow the permission access form Settings=&gt;App Info=&gt;Allow all the permission</string>
    <string name="tw_permission_tip">Requesting Permissions</string>
    <string name="tw_permission_wushenqing">Permission denied. Without this permission the app is not available.</string>
    <string name="tw_personal_center_account">Account:</string>
    <string name="tw_personal_center_bind_no">Unbinding</string>
    <string name="tw_personal_center_bindemail">Bind Mail</string>
    <string name="tw_personal_center_bindphone">Bind Mobile Phone</string>
    <string name="tw_personal_center_changepwd">Modify Password</string>
    <string name="tw_personal_center_changepwd2">Please enter password again</string>
    <string name="tw_personal_center_gift">Pack</string>
    <string name="tw_pinglun_suc">Rating successfully</string>
    <string name="tw_please_login">Please log in first</string>
    <string name="tw_progress_wait">Please wait...</string>
    <string name="tw_pwd_length_tip">Please enter password of 6 to 20 digits</string>
    <string name="tw_pwd_success">Modify password successfully</string>
    <string name="tw_quick_bind_mail">Bind mail now</string>
    <string name="tw_quick_bind_tel">Binding mobile phone now</string>
    <string name="tw_quick_reg">Quick Sign in</string>
    <string name="tw_rand_account">Random account</string>
    <string name="tw_rand_checkcode">Please enter mail verification code</string>
    <string name="tw_register_password">Please enter password</string>
    <string name="tw_register_placehoder">Please enter account</string>
    <string name="tw_register_pwd_dif">Two passwords are not matched</string>
    <string name="tw_register_text">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="tw_remain" />
    <string name="tw_remember_password">Remember password</string>
    <string name="tw_reset_success">Reset successfully</string>
    <string name="tw_resetpwd_title">Reset Password</string>
    <string name="tw_role_name">ole Name:</string>
    <string name="tw_role_name_nil">No role name yet</string>
    <string name="tw_role_tip">Role Name:</string>
    <string name="tw_safe_email">Safe Email</string>
    <string name="tw_send_fail">Send request failed</string>
    <string name="tw_send_second">Send again</string>
    <string name="tw_send_tip">Send</string>
    <string name="tw_server_tip">Server:</string>
    <string name="tw_set_password_password_again2">Confirm the password</string>
    <string name="tw_set_password_password_hint">6 to 20 characters only</string>
    <string name="tw_set_password_submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="tw_setting">Settings</string>
    <string name="tw_share_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="tw_share_fail">Share failed</string>
    <string name="tw_share_libao">Share Pack</string>
    <string name="tw_share_suc">Share successfully</string>
    <string name="tw_shequ">FB</string>
    <string name="tw_shouquan_queren">comfirm</string>
    <string name="tw_shouquan_readephonestate">「Make and manage phone calls」：Only for accessing internet purpose, in order to make sure your device has been connected to the internet successfully.</string>
    <string name="tw_shouquan_storage">Accessing to photos, media and files in the device: Applies to Customer Service Consultation only.</string>
    <string name="tw_shouquan_tip">Authorization instructions</string>
    <string name="tw_show_ensure">OK</string>
    <string name="tw_show_ensure_all">Confirm All</string>
    <string name="tw_show_password">Show password</string>
    <string name="tw_stored_value">Top-up History</string>
    <string name="tw_sure_tijiao">Ok and Submit</string>
    <string name="tw_sw_account">Switch Account</string>
    <string name="tw_swi_account">Switch account</string>
    <string name="tw_swi_account2">Switch</string>
    <string name="tw_tel_area">Region</string>
    <string name="tw_tel_area_null">Please select region</string>
    <string name="tw_tel_code">Mobile Phone Number:</string>
    <string name="tw_third_sent">Send mobile phone verification code 3 times per day</string>
    <string name="tw_tip_dis">Reminder</string>
    <string name="tw_toushu">I need help</string>
    <string name="tw_two_pwd_dif">Two passwords are not matched</string>
    <string name="tw_update_btn_tile">Update now</string>
    <string name="tw_update_content">Please download the newest version to improve game experience!</string>
    <string name="tw_update_tile">New version found</string>
    <string name="tw_user_center">User Center</string>
    <string name="tw_user_name_nil">User name can not be empty</string>
    <string name="tw_visitor_center_account">Visitor Account:</string>
    <string name="tw_visitor_login">Guest</string>
    <string name="tw_visitor_login2">Log in as visitor</string>
    <string name="tw_welcome">Welcome back:</string>
    <string name="tw_wenti_type">Type:</string>
    <string name="tw_xinxiang_info">Mail</string>
    <string name="tw_youxiaoqi_time">Validity:</string>
    <string name="ucrop_crop">Crop</string>
    <string name="ucrop_gif_tag">gif</string>
    <string name="ucrop_label_edit_photo">Edit Photo</string>
    <string name="ucrop_label_original">Original</string>
    <string name="ucrop_menu_crop">Crop</string>
    <string name="ucrop_not_crop">not supported crop type</string>
    <string name="ucrop_rotate">Rotate</string>
    <string name="ucrop_scale">Scale</string>
    <string name="upgrade_platform_account_tips">Please upgrade to platform account first</string>
    <string name="vi_cancel">Huỷ</string>
    <string name="vi_empty_tips">Bạn chưa nhập đủ thông tin, vui lòng kiểm tra lại</string>
    <string name="vi_female">Nữ</string>
    <string name="vi_finish">Xác nhận</string>
    <string name="vi_input_address">Nhập địa chỉ</string>
    <string name="vi_input_emai">Nhập email</string>
    <string name="vi_input_emailOrphone">Xin nhập email hoặc SĐT di động</string>
    <string name="vi_input_fullname">Nhập họ tên</string>
    <string name="vi_input_gender">Nhập giới tính</string>
    <string name="vi_input_id_number">Số CMND/CCCD không hợp lý, vui lòng kiểm tra lại</string>
    <string name="vi_input_issued_on">Nhập ngày cấp CMTND</string>
    <string name="vi_input_issued_place">Nhập nơi cấp CMTND</string>
    <string name="vi_input_phone_number">Nhập số điện thoại</string>
    <string name="vi_input_valid_email">Email không hợp lý, vui lòng kiểm tra lại</string>
    <string name="vi_input_valid_emailOrphone">Xin nhập email hoặc SĐT hợp lệ</string>
    <string name="vi_input_valid_phone">SĐT không hợp lý, vui lòng kiểm tra lại</string>
    <string name="vi_male">Nam</string>
    <string name="vi_not_specified">Không xác định</string>
    <string name="vi_nput_birthday">Nhập ngày sinh</string>
    <string name="vi_submit">Gửi đi</string>
    <string name="vi_submit_succeess">Gửi thành công</string>
    <string name="vi_submitting">Đang gửi</string>
    <string name="vi_title">Đăng ký</string>
    <string name="vi_underage">Rất tiếc, tài khoản đăng ký chưa đủ 18 tuổi</string>
</resources>
